leisure.com 2015-06-08

# Leisure Travel: Cheap Airline Tickets, Hotels, Car Rentals, Vacations

[Home](http://leisure.com/)Privacy Policy

**THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY STATEMENT DETAILS THE Leisure.COM PLEDGE TO KEEP YOUR INFORMATION PRIVATE.**  Any questions in regards to Leisure.com privacy practices should be sent via email to [info@Leisure.com](mailto:info@leisure.com).

Some of the web search services provided herein are provided by Trovi Search and powered by Trovi search partners. For information on the web search services data collection, please visit <http://info.trovi.com/Privacy>, and the search provider's privacy policy, as applicable.

### What type of information does Leisure.com collect?

Leisure.com utilizes the cookie feature of your browser. Cookies, on their own, can't be used to identify you. The cookie feature of your browser can be turned off; simply locate your browser preference options. Keep in mind that disabling the cookie feature will prevent you from participating in certain activities.

Your IP address helps Leisure.com diagnose server problems and helps us administer website functions. IP addresses provide us with geographical information and aggregated information on how visitors utilize Leisure.com. By monitoring search queries, access times, and traffic patterns we can determine how to market users and make their experience more enjoyable.

### What does Leisure.com do with my data?

Leisure.com only collects data to enhance and personally tailor our website to meet your needs. Personal information that is collected allows us to customize website content and generate targeted advertisements based on your particular preferences. Cookies help us distinguish between individual users, tailor fit homepages, control advertisement frequency, and so on.

IP addresses help us diagnose server issues and help us administer Leisure.com. Without your IP address it would be impossible to keep our services running 24/7, and we want to be here for you around the clock.

Every email sent to Leisure.com users is to meet your needs. We offer website updates, inform you of new features, allow you to register for special offers and sweepstakes, all for your enjoyment. If at any point these emails become annoying or bothersome, simply click on the link provided to opt out.

Also note that your email address helps Leisure.com respond to any questions you have posed, issues you have encountered, or complaints made. We require your email address so we may address these issues.

### Who else gets to see my personal information?

When you request services from our business partners Leisure.com will share your personal information with them, so that you can receive what you have requested. If you have any questions or concerns about a Leisure.com business partner, you may contact them directly. Leisure.com is not responsible for the data collection or privacy practices of business partners. Your personal information may also be shared with Leisure.com owned businesses.

Your personal information will be shared with an outside party if we have good reason to believe that the law or legal process require it. It is our obligation to protect any rights or property of Leisure.com and others associated with our company and website.

Targeted advertisements enhance user experience, and so at times we may share specifically non personal information with advertisers, so that they may present you with relevant advertisements. Geographical information may be shared along with demographics, but we will never share personally identifiable information.

Leisure shares user information to the following partners. Please visit each company's privacy policy to better understand the controls available to you.

  * Accuen Media 
  * Acxiom 
  * Ad Gear 
  * Ad Ready 
  * Adap.TV 
  * AdConion 
  * AddThis 
  * AdExpert (Microsoft) 
  * Adform 
  * AdJuggler, Inc. 
  * AdKeeper 
  * AdMedia 
  * Admotion S.R.L. 
  * Adobe 
  * Adometry 
  * AdRoll 
  * AdShuffle 
  * AdTech Inc. 
  * Advanse 
  * Advertising.com, Inc. (an AOL company) 
  * Aggregate Knowledge 
  * AKQA 
  * Alena/Performance Marketing Group (Intermix) 
  * Altitude Digital 
  * American Express (uses Omniture services) 
  * AppNexus 
  * Aranet Online 
  * Atlas DMT 
  * Bloomreach 
  * Blue Kai 
  * Brand.net 
  * Bridgetrack 
  * Brightroll 
  * BuySight 
  * C3 Metrics 
  * Caraytech S.A. (aka E-Planning) 
  * Casale 
  * Celtra 
  * Chango 
  * Cnet 
  * Cognitive Match 
  * Collective Media 
  * Comcast 
  * Compete 
  * comScore 
  * Connexity 
  * Convertro 
  * Conviva 
  * Coremetrics, Inc. 
  * Cossette Media 
  * Cox Digital Solutions (formerly Adify) 
  * Cox Enterprises 
  * Crisp Wireless 
  * Criteo Media 
  * Crowd Science 
  * DataXu 
  * Datran 
  * Diligant 
  * Dotomi 
  * DoubleClick, Inc. 
  * Dynamic Logic 
  * Epsilon 
  * Evidon 
  * Experian 
  * eyeReturn Marketing 
  * EyeView Digital 
  * EyeWonder, Inc. 
  * Facilitate 
  * Fastclick (Valueclick) 
  * FatText 
  * Flash Talking 
  * Flite 
  * Forbes 
  * Foresee 
  * FreeWheel Media, Inc. 
  * GFK 
  * GoldSpot Media 
  * Google AdSense 
  * HipCricket 
  * Hotwire 
  * Innovation Interactive (NetMining) 
  * Innovid 
  * InsightExpress 
  * Intermix (Demand Media) 
  * Interpolls 
  * Invite Media 
  * Jivox 
  * Korrelate 
  * Legolas Media 
  * LinkStorm 
  * Liquidus Marketing 
  * Locked On Media 
  * Lucid Media 
  * Markit On Demand 
  * Media6Degrees 
  * Mediaglu (formerly known as MLN Advertising) 
  * Mediamath 
  * Mediamind 
  * Mediaplex 
  * Microsoft 
  * Mixpo 
  * Moat 
  * MobileFuse 
  * Mochila 
  * Music Interactive 
  * myThings 
  * Netseer 
  * NewsRight, LLC 
  * NexTag 
  * Nielsen 
  * Optaros, Inc 
  * OsAdsPro (GroovingAds) 
  * PaperG, Inc. 
  * PayPal 
  * Phluant 
  * Pictela 
  * Planning Group International 
  * Pointdexter Systems 
  * PointRoll 
  * Predicta 
  * Pricegrabber (pgcdn.com) 
  * Procter&Gamble 
  * Pulse 360 
  * Quinstreet 
  * RadiumOne 
  * Real Media Group 
  * Rich Relevance 
  * Rocket Fuel Inc. 
  * Rovion 
  * Safecount 
  * Simpli.fi 
  * SiteScout Inc. 
  * Skenzo (Media.net) 
  * Snap 
  * Specific Media 
  * SpeedShift Media 
  * Sponge Cell 
  * Symphony Advanced Media (formerly Factor TG) 
  * Tag-Man 
  * TapAd 
  * Telemetry 
  * Teracent 
  * The Trade Desk 
  * Tidal TV/Videology 
  * TNS Customer Research Inc. 
  * TradeDoubler 
  * Tribal Fusion 
  * TruEffect 
  * TRUSTe 
  * TubeMogul 
  * Tumri 
  * Turn Inc. 
  * Undertone 
  * Unicast (Viewpoint) 
  * ValueClick Media 
  * VideoHub 
  * Vindico 
  * Visible Measures 
  * Vizu 
  * Webapps LLC dba Hitpath 
  * WebTrends 
  * Widgetbox d/b/a ClickTurn 
  * X+1 Technologies 
  * Xaxis (Media Innovation Group - mookie) 
  * Yabuka 
  * Ybrant Digital 
  * YuMe 
  * Zedo 

### How do I delete my information from Leisure.com?

At this current time it is not possible to completely delete your user information from the Leisure.com database. If you are concerned with the security of your personal data you can remove the cookie stored on your browser, which will allow the server to perceive you as a new user. In the future you can change your browser setting to not accept cookies. Be aware that removing cookies does prevent you from participating in certain activities.

### Will I be notified of a security breach?

Leisure.com has taken many steps to ensure that your personal information is not made publicly available and that is only accessible to the user who originally entered it. However, in the event of an unlikely security breach, the user will be notified via email immediately.

### Do linked sites honor your policy?

Linked sites are not run or controlled by Leisure.com. The website does contain many linked sites, so that we may offer you additional services and products that we feel you will enjoy. Each linked site is owned by an outside company; therefore, they have established their own polices in respect to privacy. Leisure.com won't be held responsible for privacy practices or policies or content of linked sites. Also note that any personal information supplied to an outside advertiser is at your own risk.

### Will your policy always remain intact?

We cannot guarantee that this policy will always be honored. In the event that Leisure.com is bought, or our assets are acquired by another company, user information may be transferred to new ownership. Leisure.com will suggest this policy be adapted, but we cannot guarantee it.

### Leisure.com will notify you of changes

Leisure.com is constantly improving and making additions to our site to provide you with better features and services. As a result, our policies must be continuously revised. Whenever alterations are required, a new revised policy will be posted to this site, along with the date of last revision. It is important to us that you are always up to date with Leisure.com policies, so check this site often for information on your privacy.

### Contacting Leisure.com

In regards to privacy issues or the collection of personal data, any questions or concerns can be directed to our dedicated representatives. Please contact them by email at [info@Leisure.com](mailto:info@accoona.com).
